We are in the midst of a group chat topic of the week
with our headliner, Teran, comedian Teran,
our headliner of the week.
And we are, we're talking about Andra Day's performance
of Lift Every Voice and Sing.
Now, of course, the bigger conversation is the fact
that every time that Black people do something,
there's always people who are like,
why are Black people doing Black people things, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So Megyn Kelly, the same lady who was mad about Black Santa,
tweeted, the so-called Black national anthem
does not belong at the Super Bowl.
She says we already have a national anthem
and it includes everyone.
Can we just, for the sake of arguments,
why would it not belong at a football game?
What is sacred about a football game
that the Negro national anthem doesn't belong there?
I agree with her.
Because it's, really?
I do, it doesn't belong there.
Neither do any of the Black players.
And to be honest, we should start our own league
and let them watch their little game
and the score be 49ers, Chiefs, Chiefs win, 3-1.
Let's go.
Let them watch that little game
and see how that goes.
Because they don't want to be,
if you don't want to be inclusive,
don't be inclusive now.
I say that about everything.
If my friends and I are playing basketball
and we play high-level basketball,
that's when I ask people to be racist then,
when a little white boy shows up
and it's like, I got next.
No, you don't.
Be racist now.
Be racist.
Look at us having a good time
and be like, you know what?
I wouldn't hire them.
I'm also not going to play with them.
Let me go over to the other court.
We are, we are, we are.
Ah.
Uh.